export const set1 = [
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["90", "88", "91", "89"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["53", "55", "58", "54"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  23</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["26", "29", "28", "30"],
    answer: "29"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  27</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "36", "37", "34"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  29</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "37", "34", "36"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  38</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["47", "49", "50", "46"],
    answer: "47"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  37</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["42", "45", "43", "41"],
    answer: "43"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["52", "55", "56", "53"],
    answer: "53"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  86</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["96", "93", "95", "94"],
    answer: "94"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  78</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["85", "88", "84", "82"],
    answer: "85"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  59</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["62", "67", "64", "66"],
    answer: "64"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["56", "55", "54", "57"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  28</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "32", "37", "34"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  29</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["31", "32", "29", "35"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  75</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["84", "83", "85", "81"],
    answer: "84"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  54</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["61", "64", "63", "62"],
    answer: "62"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["58", "59", "56", "57"],
    answer: "57"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["50", "55", "56", "53"],
    answer: "53"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  56</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["58", "63", "61", "64"],
    answer: "61"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  45</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["52", "54", "53", "55"],
    answer: "53"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  57</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["68", "65", "64", "67"],
    answer: "65"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  49</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["52", "56", "53", "55"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  68</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["78", "75", "76", "72"],
    answer: "75"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  49</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["55", "58", "60", "57"],
    answer: "58"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["92", "94", "88", "91"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  69</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["78", "75", "79", "76"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  87</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["94", "90", "92", "89"],
    answer: "92"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  45</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["56", "53", "54", "55"],
    answer: "54"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  27</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["34", "32", "35", "37"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  19</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["26", "28", "25", "23"],
    answer: "25"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["55", "58", "56", "53"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  26</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "32", "35", "33"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  84</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["91", "94", "89", "92"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  23</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["32", "31", "33", "35"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  36</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["47", "45", "46", "44"],
    answer: "44"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  49</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["57", "53", "55", "54"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["90", "85", "89", "88"],
    answer: "88"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  35</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["44", "42", "43", "45"],
    answer: "44"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  59</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["64", "62", "59", "61"],
    answer: "62"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  39</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["47", "48", "44", "46"],
    answer: "46"
  },
];
